<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Research Computing Facility</title>
 <link href="https://jdhayes.github.io/rcf//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://jdhayes.github.io/rcf//"/>
 <updated>2017-01-13T12:16:54-08:00</updated>
 <id>https://jdhayes.github.io/rcf/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Jordan Hayes</name>
   <email>jhayes@ucr.edu</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Research Computing Facility</title>
   <link href="https://jdhayes.github.io/rcf//2017/01/13/home/"/>
   <updated>2017-01-13T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>https://jdhayes.github.io/rcf//2017/01/13/home</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;welcome&quot;&gt;Welcome&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our facility’s mission is to provide…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;services&quot;&gt;Services&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RCF provides access to high-performance compute resources, data analysis and programming expertise.
The resources serve scientists at UC Riverside to master the bigdata and informatics needs of their research in a proficient and cost-effective manner. 
The following services are offered:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Development and maintenance of a high-performance informatics hardware and software infrastructure for our research community at UCR.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Instruction of hands-on tutorials and workshops on a wide variety of bioinformatic topics. Extensive manuals for these tutorials are available on our manual page.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Custom data analysis and consultation services for bioinformatics and cheminformatics projects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Establishment of research collaborations with experimental scientists from different departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;facility-description&quot;&gt;Facility Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Latest facility description for grant applications: &lt;a href=&quot;http://biocluster.ucr.edu/~rkaundal/Documents/HPC_Facility_Description.pdf&quot;&gt;Facility Description&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;More detailed information can be found on our software and hardware pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rates&quot;&gt;Rates&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annual User Registration Fee&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The annual registration fee of $1,000 gives all members of an UCR lab access to our high-performance compute infrastructure.
The registration provides access to the following resources:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Over 2500 CPU cores, ~2PB disk space, 512GB-1TB of memory/node, etc. More details are available on the compute hardware page.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Over 500 software packages and all common research databases. More details are available on the software page.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Free attendance of all our bioinformatics workshops&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Free consultation services (up to 1 hour per month).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Programming and Data Analysis Service for UCR Customers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$52 per hour labor time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More detailed information about our service rates can be found here: Bioinformatics Core &lt;a href=&quot;http://biocluster.ucr.edu/~rkaundal/Documents/Recharge_Rates.pdf&quot;&gt;Recharging Rates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contacts&quot;&gt;Contacts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thomas Girke, Director of Research Compute Facility&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jordan Hayes, Systems Administrator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Austin Leong, Systems Administrator, Assistant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;location&quot;&gt;Location&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1207 G/E Genomics Building&lt;br /&gt;
3401 Watkins Drive&lt;br /&gt;
University of California&lt;br /&gt;
Riverside, CA 92521&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
